Guide to the Norfolk County, Collection of English Deeds ca. 1409-ca.1826
University of Chicago Library
- Deed (Copyhold), 10 December 15 George II (1741) 1. Thomas Kant 2. James Kant Manor of Surlingham (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Deed (Copyhold), 25 October 17 George II (1743) 1. Mathew Barker 2. Mary Barker Manor of Framingham Earle (1/2 acre with a messuage) (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Deed (Copyhold - reversion), 21 October 22 George II (1748) 1. Mary Keeble 2. John Keeble Manor of Bungay Soke (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Deed (Copyhold), 8 December 1774 1. Mathew Pepper Manby, Esq. 2. John Mansfield of Denver 1 acre in Manor of Easthall in Denver (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Deed (Copyhold), 11 October 1784 1. William Rumball 2. Sarah Rumball 2 rods in Downham Market; Manor of Westhall in Denver (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Deed (Copyhold), 27 October 1784 1. Sarah Rumball 2. Jermyn Pratt of Watlington, clerk Land of Stow Bardolph (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Deed (Copyhold), 14 February 1785 1. Sarah Rumball 2. Jermyn Pratt of Watlington, clerk 2 rods in Downham Market; Manor of Westhall in Denver NORFOLK 23 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Will, 20 February 1739 Ann Barsham of King's Lynn Lands, etc. in Carbrook, Norfolk (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Will, 15 November 1768 Richard Cooke of Norwich, innkeeper (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Document, 1 February 1778 John Cobb of Swaffham, butcher Lands in Swaffham (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Will, 7 September 1802 Robert Batterby of Swaffham (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Will, 20 July 1805 Robert Emerson of Swaffham, surgeon (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 2 documents, Will 19 August (probated) Catherine Wilson of the Parish of East Dereham, Norfolk Receipt of Stamp Office for duties paid (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Will, 4 June 1683 Isaac Slape of Trymingham, seaman Land in Trymingham (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Will, 11 May 1701 Richard Dix of South Reps (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Will, 30 October 1708 Ann Keping of Foulden Land in Gooderston (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Will (Certificate showing Probation), 12 November 1711 Priscillie Gayford (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Will, 23 October 1712 Thomas Beates of East Harling, yeoman Land in Melland Hall, Suffolk (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Will, 5 August 1714 Rebeccah Linge of Hilborough (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Will, 16 April 1718 Anthony Peterson of Parish of Kimberly (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Will, 26 May 1724 Edmond Dix of Gymingham, carpenter (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Will, 18 November 1729 John Tuffield of Woodton of Norfolk (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Will, 30 October 1731 Thomas Marsters of Dereham Market Lands in Shipham, Norfolk (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Particular, Lands leased by Miles Rivett from John Burkin for 7 years Lands lyeing in South Walshan, Upton and Fisshley, Beighton, Sometatall (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Schedule or Particular of documents which Edmund Cocke, mercer of Norwich, delivered to William Rogers of Norwich, lynnen draper, for the use of Tho. Rogers of Darsingham concerning houses, tenements, etc. in the parish of St. Andrewe in Norwich which were mortgaged by Edmund Cocke to Thomas Rogers (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Norfolk, Quarter Sessions, 10 April 1695 Order by Court to Dikereeves of the Towneship of Cleuchwharton to repair a drain (Box 8, Folder 8)
- County Sessions, King's Lynn, 12 June 2 George II (1729) Authorizing a tax of a penny an acre by the Dikereeves of Tilney (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Quarter Sessions, King's Lynn, 19 February 9 George II (1735) Authorization for the repair of the Sea Banks about King's Lynn (Box 8, Folder 10)
- County Session, King's Lynn, 16 March 1735 Authorization to borrow money for the repair of the Sea Banks about King's Lynn (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Apprenticeship, 15 January 1761 Henry Watkins apprentice to Richard Bartram, mariner of Yarmouth (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Apprenticeship, 13 March 1769 John Kinner apprentice to Richard Bartram, mariner of Yarmouth (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Will and related documents, 2 December 1820 Theososia Webster of Dereham (the will) Two receipts to Peter Martineaus for payment of death duty Three receipts to J. S. Danield for same 30 November 1825 Memorandum concerning the voiding of the provision of the will of Theodosia Webster by the Court of Chancery Letter (will) 26 February 1826, St. Albans Peter Martineau to Edw. Foss, jr., London concerning estate of Theodosia Webster (Box 8, Folder 14)